Guide to Rice University Art Collection Acquisitions Records, 1947-1995 UA 156
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Accessions Files, 158447
  - 1986.6 W. Gutmann Sculpture, 158703 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - 1986.7 Miguel Conde Etching, 158704 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - 1986.8 William Tuite Samovar, 158705 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - 1987.1 Korean Bronze, 158706 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - 1987.2 Chinese Porcelain, 158707 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - 1987.3 Korean Earthenware, 158708 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - 1987.4 Korean Sillaware, 158709 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - 1987.5 Korean Celadon, 158710 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - 1987.6 Korean Bowl, 158711 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - 1987.7 Korean Jar, 158712 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - 1987.8 Korean Celadon, 158713 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - 1987.9 Thai Bowl, 158714 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - 1987.11 Henry Miller Watercolor "Columbine and Pulcinello", 158715 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - 1987.12 Lilic Schatz Silkscreen, 158716 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - 1987.15 Dai Tsien Prints, 158717 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - 1987.16 Dai Tsien Lithograph "Cinnabar Lotus", 158718 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - 1987.17 Dai Tsien Lithograph "Mountain Monastery...", 158719 (Box 6, Folder 42)
  - 1987.18 Dai Tsien Lithograph "Shrike Amidst ...", 158720 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - 1987.19 Dai Tsien Lithograph "Hanging Gibbon...", 158721 (Box 6, Folder 44)
  - 1987.20-21 Japanese Porcelain, 158722 (Box 6, Folder 45)
  - 1987.22 Japanese Imari, 158723 (Box 6, Folder 46)
  - 1987.23a-j Hokusai Woodcuts, 158724 (Box 6, Folder 47)
  - 1987.24a-c Yoshu Shuen Woodcuts, 158725 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - 1987.25-26 Japanese Books, 158726 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - 1987.27 Hokusai Woodcut, 158727 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - 1987.28-29 Japanese Books, 158728 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - 1987.30-34 Hokusai Woodcut "View of Mt. Fuji", 158729 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - 1987.35 Japanese Bronze, 158730 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - 1987.36 Hokusai Woodcut, 158731 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - 1987.37-44 Japanese Woodcuts, 158732 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - 1988.1 Goodman, Jill Photos, 158733 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - 1988.2 J. Pollet Oil "La Luzege", 158734 (Box 6, Folder 57)
  - 1989.1 Karl Jensen Acrylic "Take 'Em Up To '80", 158735 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - 1989.2 Karl Jensen Acrylic, 158736 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - 1989.3-4 Posters International Festival, 158737 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - 1990.1 Eduardo Chillida Lithograph " - En Noir", 158738 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - 1990.2 William Hogarth Etching, 158739 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1990.3 William Hogarth Etching "Actresses in Barn", 158740 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - 1990.4 William Hogarth Etching, 158741 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - 1990.5 Daumier Lithograph "Une Profession de Foi", 158742 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - 1990.6 Daumier Lithograph "Un M. De Vin...", 158743 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - 1990.7 Daumier Lithograph "Un Lecon de Hautes...", 158744 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - 1990.8 Daumier Lithograph "Les Plaisirs...", 158745 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - 1990.9 Jean Morin Etching "Michel de Marillac", 158746 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - 1990.10 Bill Condon Lithograph "The Sewing", 158747 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - 1990.11 Beth Van Hoesen Etching "Portofino", 158748 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1990.12 Olivier Seguin Casein, 158749 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - 1990.13 Jean Sasiano Woodcut "Dial 911", 158750 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - 1990.14-15 Kubelik Pastels, 158751 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - 1990.16 Enrique Climent Monoprint "Cabeza de Vitrol", 158752 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - 1990.17 Zao-Wou-Ki Etching "Paysage de la Mer", 158753 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - 1990.18 Francisco Pena Etching, 158754 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - 1990.19 Larry C. Graeber Lithograph "Comal Cotton", 158755 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - 1990.20 LeTraquenard Etching, 158756 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - 1990.21 Lowell Collins Woodcut "INRI", 158757 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - 1990.22 Alessandro Specchi Etching "Veduta del Palazzo", 158758 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - 1990.23 Kurt Blum Photo, 158759 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - 1990.24 Reprint Photo, 158760 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - 1990.25-31 Edward Weston Photos, 158761 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - 1990.32 S.W. Hayter Etching "Invocation", 158762 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - 1990.33 Mauric Vlaminck Lithograph "Paysage", 158763 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - 1990.34 Pierre Alechinsky Lithograph "Tablets", 158764 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - 1990.37 S.W. Hayter Etching "Invocation", 158765 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - 1990.38 Fondation Maeght Chagall Poster, 158766 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - 1990.42 Patsy Hernandez Monoprint, 158767 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - 1992.10 Georges Rouault Drypoint "Des Ongles et Dubec", 158768 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - 1992.14 Ken Wood Lithograph "Housification", 158769 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - 1992.15 Ken Wood Lithograph "Many Red Devils", 158770 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - 1992.16 Grace Spaulding John Oil "Smoke, Steam, and Mist", 158771 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - 1992.17 Grace Spaulding John Oil "Herself", 158772 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - 1992.18 Grace Spaulding John Oil "Allen's Landing", 158773 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - 1992.19 Ken Wood Acrylic "Dangerous Kitchen", 158774 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - 1992.20 Ken Wood Acrylic "Naked Lunch", 158775 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - 1992.21 Charles Pebworth Metal Relief, 158776 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - 1992.22-34 Adrienne Patton Photos, 158777 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - 1992.40 Dorothy Hood Oil "Extension of the Sky", 158779 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - 1992.41 John Casbarian Acrylic "On the Twelfth Day...", 158780 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - 1993.1 Jeff Barnum Lithograph "Self- Portrait", 158781 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - 1993.2 Jeff Barnum Lithograph "Goodbye", 158782 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - 1993.3 Jeff Barnum Pastel, 158783 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - 1993.4-12 Constance Estep Wells Monotypes, 158784 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - 1993.14a-b Chinese Scrolls, 158785 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - 1994.1-3 Jennifer Blythe Johnston Acrylics, 158786 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - 1994.4-5 Jennifer Blythe Johnston Lithographs, 158787 (Box 7, Folder 49)
- Series II: Donor/Artist Files, 158778
  - Albok, John, 158788 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Anuszkiewicz, Richard, 158789 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Appel, Karel, 158790 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Argossy Partners/Bond Street Partners, 158791 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Bardin, C. Wayne, 158792 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Boice, Mrs. Arthur, 158793 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Bolotowsky, Ilya, 158794 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bowan, Robert and Sylvia, 158795 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Bravo, Alvarez, 158796 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Britton, Mr. and Mrs. James L., 158797 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Broker, Karin, 158798 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Bukowski, John, 158799 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Camfield, William A. and Virginia, 158800 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Canter, Leslie Logan; Perryman, Kendal Canter, 158801 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Casbarian, John, 158802 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Chapman, Mr. and Mrs. David, 158803 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Chavanne, Harry and Hazel, 158804 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Cherry, Robert F., 158805 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Chillman, James, 158806 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Christo, 158807 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Clark, Leon Wilson, 158808 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Cole, Charles, 158809 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Colescott, Warrington, 158810 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Cooper, Michael, 158811 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Corbin, Jeffry, 158812 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Cullinan, Nina, 158813 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Davis, Mr. and Mrs. Tom, 158814 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Doisneau, Robert, 158815 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Donson, Theodore B., 158816 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Dorfman, Bruce, 158817 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Dunlap, Mr. and Mrs. Henry, 158818 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Englander and Keesee, Inc., 158819 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Flavin, Dan, 158820 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Goya, Francisco, 158821 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Grayson, Marion L., 158822 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Grooms, Red, 158823 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Guerrero, Jairo, 158824 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Harithas, Ann Robinson, 158825 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Heizer, Michael, 158826 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Heyne, Dr. and Mrs. Edward F. III, 158827 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Hockney, David, 158828 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - HOM Gallery, 158829 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Hood, Dorothy, 158830 (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Horner, Dr. and Mrs. Layton, 158831 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Houston International Festival, 158832 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Hutchison, Elizabeth S., 158833 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Jensen, Karl, 158834 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Johnson, Richard, 158835 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Joki, Robert, 158836 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Keightley, Patricia John, 158837 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Keller, Theo, 158838 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Kelly, Ellsworth, 158839 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Kepes, Gyorgy, 158840 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Khan, Mr. and Mrs. Michael W., 158841 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Kilgore, Mr. and Mrs. Boyd, 158842 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Kiper, Richard L., 158843 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Knight, Dr. and Mrs. Vernon, 158844 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - de Kuffner, Tamara, 158845 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Lederer, Mr. and Mrs. Al C., 158846 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Lipchitz, Jacques/Gertrude Stein, 158847 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Lohse, Richard Paul, 158848 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - London Arts Group, 158849 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - McAshan, June, 158850 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - McGinty, Martha Evelyn, 158851 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - McKnight, Lyndon, 158852 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - McVey, William, 158853 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Mears, Herbert, 158854 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Mitchell, William E., 158855 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Motherwell, Robert, 158856 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Muldawer, Kate S., 158857 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Nance, Mr. and Mrs. James K., 158858 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Neel, Alice, 158859 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - O'Neil, John, 158860 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Owen, Mrs. Kenneth Dale, 158861 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Parsons, David, 158862 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Peterkin, George Jr., 158863 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Peterson, Leslie T., 158864 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Pitman, H. Russell, 158865 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Pitman, Mavis C. [Prize], 158866 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Poulos, Basilios, 158867 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Rauschenberg, Robert, 158868 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Rice, William Marsh, 158870 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Romansky, Alvin, 158871 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Roten Galleries, Inc., 158872 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Roth, Leonard S., 158873 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Rudolph, Alice, 158874 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Sarofim, Fayez, 158875 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Sarofim, Louisa, 158877 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Scaglione, Albert, 158878 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Setser, Steven M., 158879 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Sewall Estate, 158880 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Sherar, Mr. and Mrs. Stuart, 158881 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Shorr, Harriet, 158882 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Sikora, Zdzislaw R., 158883 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Skaggs, Ray H., 158884 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Steambarge, Jim, 158886 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Stedman, Betty Ann, 158887 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Stillman, Amy, 158888 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Swartz, Beth Ames, 158889 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Turner, Mr. and Mrs. Roy C. III, 158890 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Walker, Mrs. William, 158891 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Walter P. Moore and Associates, Inc., 158892 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Wight, Frederic S., 158893 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Wilson, Mr. and Mrs. Richard O., 158894 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Winningham, Geoff, 158895 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Wrightsman, Charles B., 158896 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Zapata Corporation, 158897 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Series III: Administrative Files, 158898
  - Accessions Logs, 158899 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - African Art, 158900 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - African Art Appraisal, 158901 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Appraisers/Appraisals, 158902 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Art Collection Committee, 158903 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Auction-African Art, 158904 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Audit, 1972; 158905 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Audit, 1978; 158906 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Audit, 1982; 158907 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - [Alleged] Bierstadt Painting, 158908 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Bills and Receipts, 158909 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Collection Management, 158910 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Condition Reports, 158911 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Conservation Work, 158912 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 158913 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Arts Council of Houston/Rice Agreement, 1995; 158914 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Deaccessioned Items, 158915 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Deaccessioning Procedures, 158916 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Framing, 158917 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - History of Collection, 158918 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Images, 158919 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Inventories, 158920 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Load Requests, 158921 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Loans - Campus, 158922 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Loans-Cohen House, 158923 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Loans - Off Campus, 158924 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Loans - President's House, 158925 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Loans - President's Office, 158926 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Loans - Provost's Office, 158927 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Loans - Residential Colleges, 158928 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Menil Collection, 158929 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Missing Items, 158930 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Mission, 158931 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Patricia Toomey Memorial, 158932 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Pre-Columbian Art, 158933 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Stolen Items, 158934 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - William Pahlmann Associates, Inc., 158935 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Acquisition log, 1947, 1954, 1965-1994 (Box 13)